(Bernadette:)How come this one's on
the back of an eviction notice?
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah.
Uh, now that you mention it...
(Stuart:)can I live here?
(Bernadette:)Stuart, we'd love
to help you out,
but this a bad time;
we're about to have a baby.
(Stuart:)Or is that why
this is a great time?
(Sheldon:)Think about it--
when that baby comes,
(Stuart:)you're gonna need all the help
you can get.
(Howard:)Thank you,
(Bernadette:)but I'm not really sure.
(Howard:)Hang on, maybe it's
not the worst idea.
(Howard:)I mean, he did do a good job
taking care of my mother.
(Stuart:)That woman didn't get heat rash
once with me on powder patrol.
(Leonard:)Hey...
(Bernadette:)I guess you could stay
for a few days
(Bernadette:)and we'll see how it goes.
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Stuart:)And it's only temporary,
(Stuart:)just till I get back on my feet.
(Stuart:)or the baby goes off to college,
whichever happens first.
(Howard:)When would you move in?
(Stuart:)Well, uh, my car broke down
in your driveway,
(Stuart:)so I'm gonna say now.